

Details

Colombia +573228928385 julian0877@hotmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

Skills

SEO

Content coordination.

HTML5

CSS

JavaScript

Java

Python

Git

Wordpress

Languages

Spanish

English

Profile

System technician with an emphasis on programming, SEO specialist, content coordinator, and currently pursuing a degree in systems engineering. Fully bilingual front-end developer, responsible, punctual, creative, with strong interpersonal skills, and a very positive attitude towards any assigned task. Additionally, I possess excellent proficiency in information and communication technologies, along with extensive technical knowledge of both professional and personal hardware.

Employment History

SEO specialist and front-end developer., Zen Agency, Wyoming, PA

2022 – PRESENT

SEO specialist, content coordinator, and web developer responsible for optimizing web pages using tools and programming languages such as HTML, JavaScript, WordPress, etc. I have improved the web positioning of various companies in different industrial sectors through content creation and the implementation of SEO techniques.

Companies I have worked with:

Candlewic.com

RomanticDepot.com

Contractorslicenseguru.com

Jamesduva.com

Actionplumbing24.com

Janerichwellness.com

Caseydental.com

Drlorengrossman.com

Romanticdepot.com/store

Archcuttingtools.com

Redapplelipstick.com

JECplumbing.com (under development)

Advancedarms.com (under development)

And many more.

${\sf SEO}\ specialist\ and\ full-stack\ developer., OptimoWeb, Minden, NV$

2023 - PRESENT

SEO specialist, content creator, and web developer responsible for optimizing web pages using tools and programming languages such as HTML, JavaScript, WordPress, etc. I have improved the web positioning of various companies in different industrial sectors through content creation and the application of SEO techniques.

Companies worked with:

kitanano.com

Front-end developer and SEO specialist, Hotel Santana fusa, Fusagasuga

Front-end developer responsible for creating a static website from scratch for Santana Fusa Hotel, located in Fusagasugá, Cundinamarca. Additionally, I provide technical support, customization, and updates to this business.

Education

Elementary and High School education., Colegio San Pedro, Madrid (Cundinamarca)

JANUARY 2012 - DECEMBER 2018

Programming technician., Sena, Madrid (Cundinamarca)

JANUARY 2017 - DECEMBER 2018

Systems engineering., Universidad de Nariño, Pasto (Nariño)

MARCH 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2023

Mision TIC 2022 | Programming Diploma, Universidad Sergio Arboleda, Bogotá

MARCH 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

References

Amina Covrk from Zen Agency

amina@zen.agency | +387 62 895 070

Juan Reyes from OptimoWeb

juan@optimo.com | +57 314 8684158

Cesar Raul Gonzalez Erazo from Hotel Santana Fusa

gonzalezcesitar@gmail.com | +57 322 213 1310

Willye Piedris from Teleperformance

wpiedris@gmail.com | +57 321 475 0540

Ingrid Johana Salazar from Teleperformance

johanasagu@gmail.com | +57 313 624 1984